hash
Wars uh well Jay's starts his tour today
with his wife B once uh and because
nothing is more hardcore than riding
around on a bus and playing shows with
your family so in honor of J and B's
tour tonight's hashtag is make a rapper
soft make a rapper
soft examples would be Lil Wayne Brady
or 50 Cent of a woman or will I am
Sonoma uh I'm going to put 60 seconds on
the clock and go Steve Burn bust a
nursery rhymes yes bust a nursery rhymes
punch Rood Jun two live dinner Crews yes
punch uhuh Owen Snoop Doggy Daycare yes
Bud Owen
again Owen dominating the buzzer
BMX oh God yes points points God damn it
Owen is shutting everyone out for relish
yes Steve Burn you're in 50 sensitive
yes points excellent kid cuddle yes kid
cuddle points roywood junr
[Music]
UTI that explains points see burn bone
hugs and Harmony yes good points
excellent Roy wood junr soldja Boys and
Girls Club of America very nice softer
but very nice I like
it